

THERESA NEATE

QUALITY+ENGINEERING / DEVOPS / DEVELOPER RELATIONS / LEADERSHIP / COACH / MENTOR

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

Theresa Neate is a QA practice lead & developer advocate, with several years of leadership experience, who loves lean and agility and advocates for holistic system quality and systems thinking. (Please note: NOT a "DevOps Engineer".)

TOP VALUES

- Technical Excellence
- Empathic Leadership
- Strategy

COMMUNITY PRESENCE

- **DevOps Girls** co-founder & co-organiser (https://twitter.com/DevOpsGirls)
- Public Speaker Australia & NZ: https://theresaneate.net/#speak
- Workshops & Webinars: https://theresaneate.net/#workshop
- Coaching & Mentoring: women in public speaking (DevOps Girls)
- **Publications**: https://theresaneate.net/#pubs

CAREER HISTORY

Head Of / Practice Area Lead - Quality Engineering

Slalom Build | Sept 2020 - present

Quality Manager / QA Practice Lead

REA Group (Consumer) | Jun 2019 - Sep 2020 REA Group (Residential) | Feb 2016 - Jun 2018

Senior Developer Advocate

REA Group | June 2018 - June 2019

Lead Agile QA

Australia Post | Jan 2013 - Jan 2016

Lead Quality Analyst

REA Group | Aug 2012 - Dec 2012

Senior QA Consultant

ThoughtWorks | Aug 2009 - Aug 2012

Senior Tester, Helpdesk, Executive Manager, Team Lead, Trainer & Tutor

Various | pre-2000 - 2009

STRENGTHS

- System thinking
- Leadership
- Technical literacy and strong interest
- A range of technical skills, most at the level of "serious playing" and some at "full time specialist" level (including networking, a range of AWS services, Java, JavaScript, Python, Ruby, Buildkite, Docker, Linux, Selenium, SQL, etc.)
- Critical thinking & strategy
- Strong communication skills
- Public Speaking
- · Coaching & Mentoring
- Quality Analysis & Testing

CONTACT DETAILS

Email: theresanmail@icloud.com **Website**: https://theresaneate.net

Github: https://github.com/theresaneate
LinkedIn: https://twitter.com/in/neatet/
Twitter: https://twitter.com/TheresaNeate

Location: Melbourne Australia

TRAINING & EDUCATION

Diploma of Networking

Swinburne University of Technology (Dec 2019)

Graduate Certificate: Business IT

RMIT University (2016)

(withdrawn) Bachelors of IT & Systems

Monash University (2014)

Diploma of IT (General)

Victoria University (2010)

Diploma of IT (Web)

Victoria University (2010)

Diploma of Computer Science

South Africa (pre-2000)

Several short courses & certifications

Including ISTQB, ISEB, PACT, CCNA2, Ethical Hacking (Web Security), etc. Currently receiving professional coaching in executive leadership.